[Music]
loma linda is so special but people live
a really long time it's unique
[Music]
I've seen people playing pickleball at
tournaments like in their 90's swimming
every day
[Music]
there's so many opportunities to eat
healthy to exercise to socialize with
friends there's a lot of things that are
sort of catering to living a long life
before mom and I are very close
she worked her whole life so that you
know my sister and I could have what
everything that we needed she always
tells me she's worried about me because
not being able to save for when I get
old
retirement is I think about it every day
I should have saved you were and I
didn't and it keeps me up at night
honestly I'm going through a difficult
time I was early retired but I do still
some work because I need to have some
supplemental income but I'm okay I will
have ten jobs if I have to do it my mom
taught me to be a survivor and I'm doing
what I need to do
[Music]
Oh